这是二零一九年普通高等学校招生
全国统一考试英语科听力部分。
该部分分为第一、第二
两节。
注意。
回答听力部分时，请先将答案标在试卷上。
听力部分结束前，你将有两分钟的时间
将你的答案转涂到答题卡上。
现在是听力试音时间。
Hello, I read about your club in the paper today, and I thought I'd phone to find
out a bit more.
Yes, certainly. Well, we're a sort of social club for people from different
countries. It's quite a new club.
We have about 50 members at the moment, but we're growing all the time.
That sounds interesting.
I'm British, actually, and I came to Washington about three months ago.
I'm looking for ways to meet people.
What kinds of events do you organise?
Well, we have social get -togethers and sports events, and we also have language
evenings. Could you tell me something about the language evenings?
Yes. Every day except Thursday, we have a language evening.
People can come and practice their languages, you know, over a drink or something.
We have different languages on different evenings.
Monday, Spanish, Tuesday, Italian, Wednesday, German, and Friday, French.
On Thursday, we usually have a meal in a restaurant for anyone who wants to come.
Well, that sounds great.
I really need to practice my French.
Okay, well, if you can just give me your name and address, I'll send you the form
and some more information.
If you join now, you can have the first month free.
试音到此结束。
听力考试正式开始。
请看听力部分第一节。
of After three A, B, and
第一节，听下面五段对话，
每段对话后有一个小题。
从题中所给的
三个选项中选出最佳选项。
听完每段对话后，你都有十秒钟的时间
来回答有关小题和阅读下一小题。
Read Excuse me, can you tell me how much the shirt is?
每段对话仅。
读一遍。
例如，现在你有五秒钟的时间
看试卷上的例题。
你将听到以下内容。
Yes, it's paper.
你将有五秒钟的时间，
将正确答案标在试卷上。
衬衫的价格为九磅十五便士。
所以你选择
option to Excuse me, how can I find the book called The Class of
项，并将其画在试卷上。
现在你有五秒钟的时间
阅读第一小题的有关内容。
Oh, I'm afraid it was sold out.
It's all right.
Thank you. How did your dancing lesson go today?
Exciting, but it was hard work.
I really need a rest now.
Yeah, I can see that.
Go and get relaxed.
How much is that in total?
One hundred dollars.
But if you have a membership card, I can give you a 20 discount.
Great. This is my membership card.
Jane, I'm going out for a while.
But you have an appointment with Mr.
Douglas at three o
Well, please make it another day.
David said he would quit his job at our school.
Really? Why would he do that?
His friend started a firm in London.
She wanted David to help her.
第一节到此结束。
第二节，听下面五段对话或独白。
每段对话或独白后有几个小题，
从题中所给的
三个选项中选出最佳选项。
听每段对话或独白前，你将有时间
阅读各个小题，每小题
五秒钟。
听完后，各小题。
你将给出五秒钟的作答时间。
relevant content of the first question.
每段对话或独白读两遍。
听下面一段对话，回答第六和第七
两个小题。
现在，你有十秒钟的时间
阅读这两个小题。
Shouldn't it be in the cupboard?
I just checked.
It wasn't there.
Impossible. That was where I usually put it.
Did you check the balcony?
Yes, of course.
Couldn't find it.
Well, just get a new one then.
I'm going out for shopping.
Do you need anything?
Oh, yeah. I can't find my umbrella.
Can you buy one?
I can't find my can't find find umbrella.
find can't can't umbrella.
I can't umbrella.
听下面一段对话，回答第八至第十
三个小题。
现在你有十五秒钟的时间
阅读这。
三个小题。
Hi, Lucy. How was your weekend?
Great. You know, we went mountain climbing in the forest park.
The air was so different from the city.
Cool and fresh.
Sounds great. Yeah.
There wasn't a cloud in the sky, and we could see for miles from the top.
What about you?
What did you do?
Busy packing. Oh, yes, of course.
I forgot you and Jenny are moving into a new house.
It's on Wednesday, isn't it?
Yeah, two days after.
I didn't realize there are so many things to do.
Can I help out with anything?
Um, it'd be nice if you could take care of Henry for a couple of days.
Henry? Yes, my dog.
Oh, sure. No problem.
You just focus on the move.
Hi, Lucy. How was your weekend?
Great. You know, we went mountain climbing in the forest park.
The air was so different from the city.
Cool and fresh.
Sounds great. Yeah.
There wasn't a cloud in the sky, and we could see for miles from the top.
What about you?
What did you do?
Busy packing. Oh, yes, of course.
I forgot you and Jenny are moving into a new house.
It's on Wednesday, isn't it?
Yeah, two days after.
I didn't realize there are so many things to do.
Can I help out with anything?
Um, it'd be nice if you could take care of Henry for a couple of days.
Henry? Yes, my dog.
Oh, sure. No problem.
You just focus on the move.
听下面一段对话，回答第十一至第十三
三个小题。
现在你有十五秒钟的时间
阅读这三个小题。
Hello, can I speak to Mr.
please? Hello, but I'm afraid Mr.
Stone is in a meeting until lunchtime.
Can I take a message?
Well, yes. I'd like to make an appointment to see him.
It's Harrison White here.
Just a second, Mr.
White. I'll look in the diary.
So when's convenient for you?
Sometime today, if possible.
I hear he'll be away tomorrow.
Yes, that's right.
He'll be on a business trip for a week.
I need to talk about my new program with him before he leaves.
It's urgent. So would this afternoon be okay?
Let me see.
Okay, Mr. Stone is free this afternoon after three o Well,
three o is a bit difficult, but I could make it after three thirty.
So shall we say a quarter to four this afternoon in Mr.
Stone's office? That's great.
Thanks. Hello, can I speak to Mr.
Stone, please? Hello, but I'm afraid Mr.
Stone is in a meeting until lunchtime.
Can I take a message?
Well, yes. I'd like to make an appointment to see him.
It's Harrison White here.
Just a second, Mr.
White. I'll look in the diary.
So when's convenient for you?
Sometime today, if possible.
I hear he'll be away tomorrow.
Yes, that's right.
He'll be on a business trip for a week.
I need to talk about my new program with him before he leaves.
It's urgent. So would this afternoon be okay?
Let me see.
Mr. Stone is free this afternoon after three o 'clock.
Well, three o is a bit difficult, but I could make it after three thirty.
So shall we say a quarter to four this afternoon in Mr.
Stone's office? That's great.
Thanks. Thank you.
听下面一段对话，回答第十四至第十六
三个小题。
现在你有十五秒钟的时间
阅读这三个小题。
Good. The reason I'm calling is that we'd like to offer you the position you were
interviewed for last Thursday.
Oh, that's great.
I was really impressed with Fix It.
I'm glad to hear it.
And we're prepared to offer you a starting salary of $55,000.
I see. And vacation time?
Oh, you get one day per month in your first year.
That is, you'll have twelve days in your first year, and then increase if you stay
longer with the company.
What would be my job title?
You'd be a junior specialist, and you'd be working under Monica Stansfield, the
department manager.
Okay. Is the salary negotiable at all?
Well, this is typical for new staff.
I see. Why don't you think about it?
I'll need to hear back from you by Wednesday.
Will that work?
Sure. No problem.
I'll let you know Tuesday afternoon.
Hello? Hi, Cindy.
This is Jake Lee at Fix It Corporation.
How are you today?
Oh, hi, Jake.
I'm fine. How are you?
Good. The reason I'm calling is that we'd like to offer you the position you were
interviewed for last Thursday.
Oh, that's great.
I was really impressed with Fix It.
I'm glad to hear it.
And we're prepared to offer you a starting salary of $55,000.
I see. And vacation time?
Oh, you get one day per month in your first year.
That is, you'll have 12 days in your first year, and then increase if you stay
longer with the company.
What would be my job title?
You'd be a junior specialist, and you'd be working under Monica Stansfield, the
department manager. Okay.
Is the salary negotiable at all?
Well, this is typical for new staff.
I see. Why don't you think about it?
I'll need to hear back from you by Wednesday.
Will that work?
Sure. No problem.
I'll let you know Tuesday afternoon.
听下面一段独白，回答第十七至第二十
四个小题。
现。
在你有二十秒钟的时间
阅读这四个小题。
Hello, everybody. Today, I'd like to share with you something about John Audubon.
John was born on April 26th, 1785.
He spent much of his childhood in France, where he spent many hours each day
outdoors painting pictures.
At the age of he moved to the United States.
Well, actually, John began his life in the U.S.
as a businessman.
However, instead of taking care of his business, John was often off exploring
nature. At first, John spent his time hunting for fun.
Then he found that the animals around were very beautiful, and he particularly
enjoyed observing the birds he saw.
He began studying them, trying to learn the differences between the birds and
noticing their different behaviors.
Therefore, he painted the birds he observed a lot.
In 1819, John realized that he didn't have enough money to pay his bills.
He was very upset that he couldn't earn enough money to support his family, so he
spent time improving his painting skills and began to sell his paintings.
He discovered that he could earn some money while doing something he really enjoyed.
We are lucky now to have so many paintings of American birds by John Audubon.
Hello, everybody. Today, I'd like to share with you something about John Audubon.
John was born on April 26th, 1785.
He spent much of his childhood in France, where he spent many hours each day
outdoors painting pictures.
At the age of 18, he moved to the United States.
Well, actually, began his life in the U.S.
as a businessman.
However, instead of taking care of his business, John was often off exploring
nature. At first, John spent his time hunting for fun.
Then he found that the animals around were very beautiful, and he particularly
enjoyed observing the birds he saw.
He began studying them, trying to learn the differences between the birds and
noticing their different behaviors.
Therefore, he painted the birds he observed a lot.
In 1819, John realized that he didn't have enough money to pay his bills.
He was very upset that he couldn't earn enough money to support his family, so he
spent time improving his painting skills and began to sell his paintings.
He discovered that he could earn some money while doing something he really enjoyed.
We are lucky now to have so many paintings of American birds by John Audubon.
第二节到此结束。
现在你有两分钟的时间
将。试卷上的答案转涂到答题卡上。
you watching! Thank you for watching!
Thank you for watching!
听力部分到此结束。